[
  {
    "questionNum": 80001,
    "questionText": " Chicken hearted",
    "answerText": " Timid"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80002,
    "questionText": " Cold war",
    "answerText": " A very unfriendly Relationship between two countries who are not actually fighting each other"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80003,
    "questionText": " Cold blooded",
    "answerText": " Showing no feelings or pity for other people"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80004,
    "questionText": " Close shave",
    "answerText": " A narrow escape"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80005,
    "questionText": " Cock and bull story",
    "answerText": " A story that is unlikely to be true but is used as an explanation or excuse"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80006,
    "questionText": " Dead against",
    "answerText": " Just opposite"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80007,
    "questionText": " Deadline",
    "answerText": " A point in time by which something must be done"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80008,
    "questionText": " Day in; day out",
    "answerText": " Every day for a long period of time"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80009,
    "questionText": " Die in harness",
    "answerText": " To die at work-place"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80010,
    "questionText": " Dead letter",
    "answerText": " A law or an agreement that still exists but that is ignored"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80011,
    "questionText": " Dark horse",
    "answerText": " One who suddenly comes into light"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80012,
    "questionText": " Dry facts",
    "answerText": " Truthfulness"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80013,
    "questionText": " Do away with",
    "answerText": " To stop doing or having something; to make something end"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80014
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80015,
    "questionText": " Do-in-the manager policy",
    "answerText": " The principle by which one does not gain oneself and the other person does not gain"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80016,
    "questionText": " Due to",
    "answerText": " Owing to; because of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80017,
    "questionText": " Double minded",
    "answerText": " Confused; have different opinions"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80018,
    "questionText": " Dead loss",
    "answerText": " A person or thing that is not helpful or useful"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80019,
    "questionText": " Dowell",
    "answerText": " To progress; to get fame"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80020,
    "questionText": " Down and out",
    "answerText": " Without money; a home or a job and living on the streets"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80021,
    "questionText": " Drop a subject",
    "answerText": " To abandon or omit a matter"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80022,
    "questionText": " Drop in on",
    "answerText": " To pay an informal visit to a person or a place"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80023,
    "questionText": " Drop out of",
    "answerText": " To no longer take part in or be part of something"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80024,
    "questionText": " Draw a line",
    "answerText": " To fix a limit"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80025,
    "questionText": " Ease someone out",
    "answerText": " To force somebody to leave a job or position of authority"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80026,
    "questionText": " Every now and then",
    "answerText": " Use to say how often something happens or is done"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80027,
    "questionText": " Escape one's lips",
    "answerText": " To speak sliply"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80028,
    "questionText": " Escape notice",
    "answerText": " Don't mind"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80029,
    "questionText": " Eat out",
    "answerText": " To have a meal in a restaurant"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80030,
    "questionText": " Eat one's words",
    "answerText": " To return one's word"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80031,
    "questionText": " Eat humble pie",
    "answerText": " To say and show that you are sorry for a mistake that you made"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80032,
    "questionText": " Far and near",
    "answerText": " Around the surroundings"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80033,
    "questionText": " For good",
    "answerText": " For good and all; for ever"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80034,
    "questionText": " For fear of",
    "answerText": " To avoid the danger of something happening"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80035,
    "questionText": " Fair and square",
    "answerText": " Honestly and according to the rules"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80036,
    "questionText": " From head to foot",
    "answerText": " Covering your whole body"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80037,
    "questionText": " For the time being",
    "answerText": " In the present time"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80038,
    "questionText": " Fast living",
    "answerText": " Luxurious life"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80039,
    "questionText": " Fish out of water",
    "answerText": " To be like one out of one's element"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80040,
    "questionText": " Fool's paradise",
    "answerText": " Foolish ideas"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80041,
    "questionText": " For nothing",
    "answerText": " Without payment"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80042,
    "questionText": " Far and away",
    "answerText": " By a very great amount"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80043,
    "questionText": " Few and far between",
    "answerText": " Not frequently ; not happening often"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80044,
    "questionText": " From bad to worse",
    "answerText": " To get even worse"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80045,
    "questionText": " From door to door",
    "answerText": " From building to building"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80046,
    "questionText": " Fair hand",
    "answerText": " Legible writing"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80047,
    "questionText": " Free lance",
    "answerText": " To earn money by selling your work to several different organizations"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80048,
    "questionText": " Face to face",
    "answerText": " In the presence"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80049,
    "questionText": " Fish in troubled waters",
    "answerText": " To exploit the unfavourable conditions"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80050,
    "questionText": " From the bottom of one's heart",
    "answerText": " Very Sincerely"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80051,
    "questionText": " Fair sex",
    "answerText": " A lady"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80052,
    "questionText": " For good and all",
    "answerText": " For ever; for good"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80053,
    "questionText": " For long",
    "answerText": " For many days; longer time"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80054,
    "questionText": " Fall into a rage",
    "answerText": " To become angry"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80055,
    "questionText": " Fall short of",
    "answerText": " To be of inferior"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80056,
    "questionText": " Fall flat on",
    "answerText": " To prove ineffective"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80057,
    "questionText": " For the purpose of",
    "answerText": " Mat is needed in a particular situation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80058,
    "questionText": " A feather of one's cap",
    "answerText": " Something to be proud of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80059,
    "questionText": " Feather one's nest",
    "answerText": " To earn by unfair means"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80060,
    "questionText": " Fellow feeling",
    "answerText": " A feeling of sympathy for somebody because you have shared similar experiences"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80061,
    "questionText": " Fight shy of",
    "answerText": " To be hesitant"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80062,
    "questionText": " Force one's hand",
    "answerText": " To force one to do unwillingly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80063,
    "questionText": " Forty winks",
    "answerText": " A siesta"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80064,
    "questionText": " Fringe benefits",
    "answerText": " Extra things that an employer gives you as well as your wages"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80065,
    "questionText": " Fair weather friend",
    "answerText": " Friends of good days only"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80066,
    "questionText": " Fall in with",
    "answerText": " To agree to something"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80067,
    "questionText": " Fall out with",
    "answerText": " To have an argument with somebody"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80068,
    "questionText": " Fall to one's lot",
    "answerText": " To become ones task or responsibility"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80069,
    "questionText": " Fall behind in",
    "answerText": " To fail to keep level"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80070,
    "questionText": " Fall a prey to",
    "answerText": " To be harmed or affected by something bad"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80071,
    "questionText": " Gala day",
    "answerText": " A special public celebration or entertainment"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80072,
    "questionText": " Good for nothing",
    "answerText": " Of no use"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80073,
    "questionText": " Gift of the gab",
    "answerText": " Ability or art of speaking fluently"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80074,
    "questionText": " Golden mean",
    "answerText": " Neither to much nor to little"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80075,
    "questionText": " Good samaritan",
    "answerText": " A person who gives help and sympathy to people who need it"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80076,
    "questionText": " Get the better of",
    "answerText": " To overcome"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80077,
    "questionText": " Get by heart",
    "answerText": " To learn orally or to remember orally"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80078,
    "questionText": " Go a long way",
    "answerText": " To continue with an activity"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80079,
    "questionText": " Golden opportunity",
    "answerText": " A very favourable chance"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80080,
    "questionText": " Get ahead of",
    "answerText": " To make progress"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80081,
    "questionText": " Get along with",
    "answerText": " To leave a place"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80082,
    "questionText": " Get away with",
    "answerText": " To steal something and escape with it"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80083,
    "questionText": " Get down to",
    "answerText": " To start to do"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80084,
    "questionText": " Get even with",
    "answerText": " To revenge"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80085,
    "questionText": " Get hold of",
    "answerText": " To find something that you want or need"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80086,
    "questionText": " Get into a soup",
    "answerText": " To make things difficult"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80087,
    "questionText": " Get in to the swing of things",
    "answerText": " To be familiar of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80088,
    "questionText": " Get on one's nerves",
    "answerText": " To have a friendly relationship with somebody"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80089,
    "questionText": " Get on with",
    "answerText": " To be worrisome"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80090,
    "questionText": " Get out of",
    "answerText": " To leave or go out of a place"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80091,
    "questionText": " Get out of line",
    "answerText": " To avoid a responsibility or duty"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80092,
    "questionText": " Get the sack",
    "answerText": " Dismiss from the services"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80093,
    "questionText": " Get the upper hand",
    "answerText": " To get an advantage"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80094,
    "questionText": " Get through with",
    "answerText": " To finish or complete a task"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80095,
    "questionText": " Get wind of",
    "answerText": " To know the secret"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80096,
    "questionText": " Get word",
    "answerText": " To be able to say anything"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80097,
    "questionText": " Give a break",
    "answerText": " To give a chance"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80098,
    "questionText": " Give a piece of mind",
    "answerText": " To scold"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80099,
    "questionText": " Give a ring",
    "answerText": " To make a telephone call"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80100,
    "questionText": " Go through fire and water",
    "answerText": " To take any risk"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80101,
    "questionText": " Go to rack and ruin",
    "answerText": " To get into a bad condition"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80102,
    "questionText": " Greenroom",
    "answerText": " A room in a theatre; television; studio"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80103,
    "questionText": " Get off scot free",
    "answerText": " To go away without punishment"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80104,
    "questionText": " Goa long way",
    "answerText": " To make progress"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80105,
    "questionText": " Hand in hand",
    "answerText": " If two people are hand in hand they are holding each other's hand"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80106,
    "questionText": " Here and there",
    "answerText": " In various place"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80107,
    "questionText": " Hard cash",
    "answerText": " Money"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80108,
    "questionText": " How and why",
    "answerText": " To express method and reason"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80109,
    "questionText": " Hard up",
    "answerText": " Having very little money"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80110,
    "questionText": " High time",
    "answerText": " To enjoy yourself very much"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80111,
    "questionText": " Hard nut to crack",
    "answerText": " A difficult problem to solve"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80112,
    "questionText": " Hang by a thread",
    "answerText": " A critical condition"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80113,
    "questionText": " Haul over the coals",
    "answerText": " To scold; chide"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80114,
    "questionText": " Have a brush with",
    "answerText": " To dispute very little; or to quarrel in a small quantity"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80115,
    "questionText": " Have a mind",
    "answerText": " Make your own decisions"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80116,
    "questionText": " Have a thing at one's fingers tips",
    "answerText": " To get knowledge completely"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80117,
    "questionText": " Have dean hands",
    "answerText": " To get innocent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80118,
    "questionText": " Have in hand",
    "answerText": " A piece of work to be in hand"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80119,
    "questionText": " Have an eye on a thing",
    "answerText": " To look at or watch something"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80120,
    "questionText": " Have one's hands full",
    "answerText": " Too busy to do something else"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80121,
    "questionText": " 15. Have too many irons in",
    "answerText": " To be engaged in too many the fire things"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80122,
    "questionText": " 16. Herculean task",
    "answerText": " Work which requires extraordinary strength to accomplish at"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80123,
    "questionText": " High and low",
    "answerText": " Everywhere"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80124,
    "questionText": " High living"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80125,
    "questionText": " 19. Hit the nail on the head",
    "answerText": " Do exactly the right thing"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80126,
    "questionText": " Hold one's tongue",
    "answerText": " Keep silence"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80127,
    "questionText": " Highhanded"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80128,
    "questionText": " 22. Hard times",
    "answerText": " Unpleasant and difficult situation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80129,
    "questionText": " 23. Have one's way",
    "answerText": " To have what you want especially by opposing other people"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80130,
    "questionText": " 1. Iron hand",
    "answerText": " With strictness"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80131,
    "questionText": " In favour of",
    "answerText": " In the side of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80132,
    "questionText": " In front of",
    "answerText": " In face of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80133,
    "questionText": " In order to",
    "answerText": " 'To' or 'for'"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80134,
    "questionText": " In quest of",
    "answerText": " In searchof"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80135,
    "questionText": " In the hope of",
    "answerText": " Tobe in hope"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80136,
    "questionText": " In case",
    "answerText": " If"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80137,
    "questionText": " In detail",
    "answerText": " Explain something fully"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80138,
    "questionText": " In no time",
    "answerText": " At once"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80139,
    "questionText": " In the teeth of",
    "answerText": " To be against"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80140,
    "questionText": " In time",
    "answerText": " Not late; with enough time to be able to do something"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80141,
    "questionText": " In connection with",
    "answerText": " For reasons connected with somebody I something"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80142,
    "questionText": " 13. In defence of",
    "answerText": " The act of protecting somebody / something from attack"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80143,
    "questionText": " In view of",
    "answerText": " Having regard to"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80144,
    "questionText": " In proportion to",
    "answerText": " In the ratio of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80145,
    "questionText": " In respect of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80146,
    "questionText": " In the face of",
    "answerText": " In despite of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80147,
    "questionText": " In point of",
    "answerText": " From the point of view"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80148,
    "questionText": " In a fix",
    "answerText": " In puzzling state"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80149,
    "questionText": " In a nutshell",
    "answerText": " In a few words"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80150,
    "questionText": " In full swing"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80151,
    "questionText": " In regard to",
    "answerText": " In comparison with"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80152,
    "questionText": " In the dark",
    "answerText": " Keep ignorant about"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80153,
    "questionText": " Instead of",
    "answerText": " In the place of somebody I something"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80154,
    "questionText": " III at ease"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80155,
    "questionText": " In vogue"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80156,
    "questionText": " Irony of fate",
    "answerText": " The amusing or strange aspect of a situation that is very different from what you expect"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80157,
    "questionText": " In all respect",
    "answerText": " With all kinds / concernings"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80158,
    "questionText": " 29. In full",
    "answerText": " Including the whole of something"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80159,
    "questionText": " 30. In fact",
    "answerText": " Indeed"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80160,
    "questionText": " 31. In the meantime"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80161,
    "questionText": " 32. In any case",
    "answerText": " Whatever happens or may have happened"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80162,
    "questionText": " 33. In force",
    "answerText": " To be in operation; going to"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80163,
    "questionText": " 34. In good faith",
    "answerText": " Without offence"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80164,
    "questionText": " 35. In hot haste",
    "answerText": " In a hurry"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80165,
    "questionText": " 36. In an instant",
    "answerText": " Within a wink"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80166,
    "questionText": " 37. In name only",
    "answerText": " Officially recognize but not existing in reality"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80167,
    "questionText": " In office",
    "answerText": " In power"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80168,
    "questionText": " In season and out of season",
    "answerText": " Every time-in good time or bad time"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80169,
    "questionText": " 40. In case of",
    "answerText": " If something happens"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80170,
    "questionText": " 41. In defiance of",
    "answerText": " Open refusal to obey"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80171,
    "questionText": " 42. In honour of",
    "answerText": " In order to show respect and admiration for somebody /something"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80172,
    "questionText": " 43. In keeping with"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80173,
    "questionText": " 44. In the eye of",
    "answerText": " According to the way that somebody see the situation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80174,
    "questionText": " 45. In place of",
    "answerText": " Instead of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80175,
    "questionText": " 46. In the interests of",
    "answerText": " In order to help or achieve"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80176,
    "questionText": " 47. In the name of",
    "answerText": " For somebody; showing that something officially belongs to somebody"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80177,
    "questionText": " In order that",
    "answerText": " So that something can happen"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80178,
    "questionText": " In the end",
    "answerText": " After a long period of time"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80179,
    "questionText": " In one's mind's eye",
    "answerText": " In the inner eye"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80180,
    "questionText": " In fault",
    "answerText": " An accused person"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80181,
    "questionText": " In due course",
    "answerText": " In chronicle"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80182,
    "questionText": " In a temper",
    "answerText": " To be angry"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80183,
    "questionText": " In course of time",
    "answerText": " When enough time has passed"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80184,
    "questionText": " Jack of all trades",
    "answerText": " One who can turn his hand to anything"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80185,
    "questionText": " 2. Jaundiced eye",
    "answerText": " To have prejudice or jealousy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80186,
    "questionText": " Jail bird",
    "answerText": " A hardened criminal"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80187,
    "questionText": " Join in with",
    "answerText": " To take part in an activity with other people"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80188,
    "questionText": " Jump to a conclusion"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80189,
    "questionText": " Keep an eye on",
    "answerText": " To be watching carefully"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80190,
    "questionText": " Keep abreast of",
    "answerText": " To make sure that you know all the most recent facts about a subject"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80191,
    "questionText": " 3. Keep in view",
    "answerText": " To mind or to care something: to keep in eyes"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80192,
    "questionText": " Keep company",
    "answerText": " The people that somebody spends time with"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80193,
    "questionText": " Keep body and soul together",
    "answerText": " For survival"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80194,
    "questionText": " Keep good time",
    "answerText": " Used to say appropriate time"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80195,
    "questionText": " Keep in mind",
    "answerText": " To remember"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80196,
    "questionText": " Keep in-touch with",
    "answerText": " To remain in contact"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80197,
    "questionText": " Keep late hours",
    "answerText": " To be awoke late night"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80198,
    "questionText": " Keep the wolf from the door",
    "answerText": " To avoid starvation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80199,
    "questionText": " Kick a habit",
    "answerText": " To stop doing something that you have done for a longtime"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80200,
    "questionText": " Kill two birds with one stone",
    "answerText": " To serve two purposes at one time"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80201,
    "questionText": " Know by sight",
    "answerText": " To recognize somebody without knowing them well"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80202,
    "questionText": " Keep one's word",
    "answerText": " To complete waiting"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80203,
    "questionText": " Lose Sight of",
    "answerText": " To become no longer able to see"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80204,
    "questionText": " Look blank",
    "answerText": " To be amazed"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80205,
    "questionText": " Lie in wait",
    "answerText": " To keep waiting for the victim"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80206,
    "questionText": " Life and soul",
    "answerText": " Life"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80207,
    "questionText": " Long and short",
    "answerText": " Summary; brief"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80208,
    "questionText": " Learn by rote",
    "answerText": " To remember something without understanding An unhappy or disappointed expression"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80209,
    "questionText": " 7 Long face",
    "answerText": " An unhappy or disappointed expression"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80210,
    "questionText": " Left handed compliment",
    "answerText": " To complain as admiration"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80211,
    "questionText": " Loose tongue",
    "answerText": " Unsettled matter"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80212,
    "questionText": " Lump sum",
    "answerText": " An amount of money that is paid at one time and not on separate occasions"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80213,
    "questionText": " Lose heart",
    "answerText": " To stop hoping for something or trying to do something because you no longer feel confident"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80214,
    "questionText": " 12. Laugh in one's sleeves",
    "answerText": " To be secretly amused about something"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80215,
    "questionText": " 13. Lend one's ear",
    "answerText": " To listen"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80216,
    "questionText": " 14. Little by little"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80217,
    "questionText": " 15. Lose one's cool",
    "answerText": " To lose control"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80218,
    "questionText": " 16. Lose one's head",
    "answerText": " To become unable to act in a calm or sensible way"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80219,
    "questionText": " 17. Lose one's way",
    "answerText": " To forget way"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80220,
    "questionText": " Make a name",
    "answerText": " To be famous; to earn name and fame"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80221,
    "questionText": " 2. Make good",
    "answerText": " To compensate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80222,
    "questionText": " 3. Make up one's mind",
    "answerText": " To determine"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80223,
    "questionText": " 4. Miss the bus",
    "answerText": " To be unable to take advantage of something because you are too late"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80224,
    "questionText": " 5. Man of parts",
    "answerText": " A man of talent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80225,
    "questionText": " 6. Man in the street",
    "answerText": " Simple man"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80226,
    "questionText": " 7. Man of action",
    "answerText": " A dutiful person"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80227,
    "questionText": " 8. Make an ass of oneself",
    "answerText": " To be foolish"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80228,
    "questionText": " Make the best of both the worlds",
    "answerText": " Benefit in both hands"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80229,
    "questionText": " Make a fortune",
    "answerText": " To become rich"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80230,
    "questionText": " Make friends",
    "answerText": " To become a friend of somebody"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80231,
    "questionText": " Make or mar",
    "answerText": " To make or spoil"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80232,
    "questionText": " Mend or end",
    "answerText": " To improve or ruin"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80233,
    "questionText": " Man of the world",
    "answerText": " An experienced man"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80234,
    "questionText": " Mind one's own business",
    "answerText": " To leave other people alone"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80235,
    "questionText": " More or less",
    "answerText": " Little or much around"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80236,
    "questionText": " Move heaven and earth",
    "answerText": " To work hard to get something"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80237,
    "questionText": " Make a fool of oneself",
    "answerText": " To be stupid"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80238,
    "questionText": " Make a mess of",
    "answerText": " To bungle"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80239,
    "questionText": " 20. Maiden name",
    "answerText": " The name of a married woman before marriage"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80240,
    "questionText": " 21. Make a hash of something",
    "answerText": " To do something badly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80241,
    "questionText": " Miss the boat",
    "answerText": " Tomiss a chance"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80242,
    "questionText": " Null and void"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80243,
    "questionText": " Now and again",
    "answerText": " Occasionally"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80244,
    "questionText": " Nip in the bud",
    "answerText": " To destroy a thing at the very beginning"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80245,
    "questionText": " A narrow escape",
    "answerText": " To be saved with a great difficulty"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80246,
    "questionText": " Neck and neck",
    "answerText": " Side by side"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80247,
    "questionText": " Night and day",
    "answerText": " To be continued (day or night)"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80248,
    "questionText": " Nine day's wonder"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80249,
    "questionText": " Now and then",
    "answerText": " Sometimes"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80250,
    "questionText": " Now or never",
    "answerText": " At present time or not in present past or future"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80251,
    "questionText": " Never mind",
    "answerText": " No matter"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80252,
    "questionText": " Off and on",
    "answerText": " Occesionelly:irregularly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80253,
    "questionText": " Of no avail"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80254,
    "questionText": " On account of",
    "answerText": " Becauseof"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80255,
    "questionText": " On no account",
    "answerText": " Not at all"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80256,
    "questionText": " Owing to",
    "answerText": " Due to"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80257,
    "questionText": " On the contrary",
    "answerText": " The opposite of the last one"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80258,
    "questionText": " To the contrary",
    "answerText": " Showing or proving the opposite"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80259,
    "questionText": " Of late",
    "answerText": " Recently"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80260,
    "questionText": " Out of question",
    "answerText": " Not possible. impossible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80261,
    "questionText": " Out and out",
    "answerText": " Completely"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80262,
    "questionText": " Over head and ears",
    "answerText": " More than enough"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80263,
    "questionText": " On the alert"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80264,
    "questionText": " On the brink of",
    "answerText": " Tobe near to"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80265,
    "questionText": " Open and above board"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80266,
    "questionText": " Once again"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80267,
    "questionText": " On the eve of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80268,
    "questionText": " Once and for all"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80269,
    "questionText": " Once for all",
    "answerText": " Forever"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80270,
    "questionText": " Of course"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80271,
    "questionText": " Out of pocket",
    "answerText": " Without money"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80272,
    "questionText": " Over and above"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80273,
    "questionText": " Of the opinion",
    "answerText": " Of the concept"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80274,
    "questionText": " On the credit",
    "answerText": " On delayed payment"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80275,
    "questionText": " 24. On an average",
    "answerText": " Dividing the total by the number of amounts"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80276,
    "questionText": " 25. On good terms"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80277,
    "questionText": " 26. On time"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80278,
    "questionText": " 27. On and on"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80279,
    "questionText": " 28. Once upon a time",
    "answerText": " Onetime"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80280,
    "questionText": " 29. On the verge of",
    "answerText": " On the point of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80281,
    "questionText": " 30. On the whole"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80282,
    "questionText": " 31. On an account",
    "answerText": " Not in any circumstences or situations"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80283,
    "questionText": " 32. Out of form",
    "answerText": " Not to be in good form"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80284,
    "questionText": " 33. Open secret"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80285,
    "questionText": " Over and over again"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80286,
    "questionText": " Out of the way",
    "answerText": " To be not in proper order"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80287,
    "questionText": " Off one's head",
    "answerText": " To be corrupt one's wit"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80288,
    "questionText": " Oily tongue",
    "answerText": " The language of flattering or a flattering tongue"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80289,
    "questionText": " On one's guard",
    "answerText": " To be aware; to be careful"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80290,
    "questionText": " On one's last legs",
    "answerText": " About to fall"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80291,
    "questionText": " On the spot"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80292,
    "questionText": " Once in a while"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80293,
    "questionText": " One and all",
    "answerText": " All"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80294,
    "questionText": " 43. Open fire",
    "answerText": " To begin firing"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80295,
    "questionText": " Open handed man",
    "answerText": " One who spends money with enthusiasm"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80296,
    "questionText": " 45. Open hearted man",
    "answerText": " A man who has an open heart"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80297,
    "questionText": " 46. Open one's mind",
    "answerText": " To give one's secret opinion"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80298,
    "questionText": " 47. Out at elbows",
    "answerText": " Poor"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80299,
    "questionText": " 48. Out of date"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80300,
    "questionText": " 19. Out of doors",
    "answerText": " Out side of the house"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80301,
    "questionText": " 50. Out of one's mind",
    "answerText": " To be mad or crazy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80302,
    "questionText": " 51. Out of temper",
    "answerText": " To be in a rage; to be iI1 an anger"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80303,
    "questionText": " 52. Over night",
    "answerText": " At night"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80304,
    "questionText": " 53. Over one's head",
    "answerText": " Not to understand; to be confused"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80305,
    "questionText": " 54. Other than"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80306,
    "questionText": " 55. On the spur of the moment"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80307,
    "questionText": " 56. On a large scale",
    "answerText": " A lot of things or persons"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80308,
    "questionText": " 57. On one's account",
    "answerText": " Cause of somebody"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80309,
    "questionText": " 58. On the strength of",
    "answerText": " On the force of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80310,
    "questionText": " 59. On all hands",
    "answerText": " By all"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80311,
    "questionText": " 61. Out of favour",
    "answerText": " To be angry; against"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80312,
    "questionText": " Part and parcel",
    "answerText": " An essential part"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80313,
    "questionText": " Pros and cons",
    "answerText": " Arguments for and against"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80314,
    "questionText": " 3. Put on end to",
    "answerText": " To be finished; to end"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80315,
    "questionText": " 4. Pandora's box",
    "answerText": " A source of evil powers"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80316,
    "questionText": " 5. Put on flesh",
    "answerText": " To be fat"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80317,
    "questionText": " 6. Play the fool",
    "answerText": " To act foolishly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80318,
    "questionText": " 7. Put someone to death",
    "answerText": " To kill"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80319,
    "questionText": " 8. Playa double game",
    "answerText": " To act dubiously"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80320,
    "questionText": " 9. Play hide and seek"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80321,
    "questionText": " 10. Pick and choose",
    "answerText": " To choose one rejecting others."
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80322,
    "questionText": " 11. Poison someone's ears",
    "answerText": " To prejudice"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80323,
    "questionText": " 12. Play false"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80324,
    "questionText": " 13. Put into action",
    "answerText": " To work"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80325,
    "questionText": " 14. Pick a quarrel with",
    "answerText": " Intentionally begin a quarrel"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80326,
    "questionText": " Pickup the late",
    "answerText": " To pay the bill of others"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80327,
    "questionText": " Pink of condition",
    "answerText": " To be healthy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80328,
    "questionText": " Playa trick on",
    "answerText": " To muse with somebody"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80329,
    "questionText": " Play second fiddle",
    "answerText": " To be in a subordinate position"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80330,
    "questionText": " Play truant"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80331,
    "questionText": " Plum oneself on",
    "answerText": " To be proud of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80332,
    "questionText": " Provide against a rainy",
    "answerText": " To save for bad time (= or days) day"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80333,
    "questionText": " 22. Pull one's punches",
    "answerText": " To criticize politely"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80334,
    "questionText": " 23. Pull one's weight",
    "answerText": " To fulfill one's duty or responsibility"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80335,
    "questionText": " 24. Pull well with",
    "answerText": " To work together"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80336,
    "questionText": " 25. Put a spoke in one's wheel",
    "answerText": " To hinder one's progress"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80337,
    "questionText": " 26. Put down in black and white",
    "answerText": " To put something in written form"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80338,
    "questionText": " 27. Put on trial",
    "answerText": " To FIR against somebody"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80339,
    "questionText": " 28. Put one's foot down",
    "answerText": " To refuse to yield"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80340,
    "questionText": " 29. Put one's shoulder to the wheel",
    "answerText": " To do the work with one's own efforts"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80341,
    "questionText": " Put one's foot in",
    "answerText": " TO do blunder"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80342,
    "questionText": " To put one's head together",
    "answerText": " To consult with each other"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80343,
    "questionText": " Put to the sword"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80344,
    "questionText": " Put to shame",
    "answerText": " To be ashamed"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80345,
    "questionText": " Put to bed",
    "answerText": " To make one sleep"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80346,
    "questionText": " Put the cart before the horse",
    "answerText": " To do things in a wrong manner; reverse order"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80347,
    "questionText": " 36. Put one out of countenance",
    "answerText": " To be ashamed"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80348,
    "questionText": " A queer fish"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80349,
    "questionText": " Quite a few",
    "answerText": " A lot of; many"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80350,
    "questionText": " Quick of understanding",
    "answerText": " One who has intelligent wit"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80351,
    "questionText": " Quarrel with one's bread"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80352,
    "questionText": " A red letter day",
    "answerText": " Auspicious day of rejoicing; lucky and important day"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80353,
    "questionText": " Rhyme or Reason",
    "answerText": " Reason"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80354,
    "questionText": " A rainy day",
    "answerText": " A time of difficulty or poverty"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80355,
    "questionText": " Run short",
    "answerText": " To reduce; shortage of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80356,
    "questionText": " Run a muck",
    "answerText": " Rush to in a frenzy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80357,
    "questionText": " Right hand man",
    "answerText": " A very- useful person on whom one can depend"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80358,
    "questionText": " Run the risk of",
    "answerText": " To take risk"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80359,
    "questionText": " Red handed",
    "answerText": " To be caught by the police during doing the crime"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80360,
    "questionText": " Root and branch",
    "answerText": " Totally"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80361,
    "questionText": " Read between the lines",
    "answerText": " To read carefully; to understand the additional meaning"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80362,
    "questionText": " Ready money",
    "answerText": " Cash rupees"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80363,
    "questionText": " Red tapism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80364,
    "questionText": " Rest on one's laurels",
    "answerText": " To rest satisfied with the honours already won; to retire from active life"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80365,
    "questionText": " Right here",
    "answerText": " At this place"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80366,
    "questionText": " Right now"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80367,
    "questionText": " Red tape",
    "answerText": " Excessive and unnecessary adherence to formalities"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80368,
    "questionText": " Rise like a phoenix from",
    "answerText": " To live a destroyed thing again its ashes"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80369,
    "questionText": " 18. To rise to the occasion",
    "answerText": " To be found equal to the task"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80370,
    "questionText": " 19. Rough guess",
    "answerText": " To guess commonly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80371,
    "questionText": " 20. Rule the roost",
    "answerText": " To keep one's possession on others"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80372,
    "questionText": " Small fry",
    "answerText": " Ordinary beings"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80373,
    "questionText": " Sine die",
    "answerText": " For uncertain period of time"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80374,
    "questionText": " Sooner or later"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80375,
    "questionText": " Set free",
    "answerText": " To release from something"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80376,
    "questionText": " Sleeping partner",
    "answerText": " An inactive partner in business"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80377,
    "questionText": " Stuff and none sense"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80378,
    "questionText": " Sum and substance"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80379,
    "questionText": " Stand somebody in good"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80380,
    "questionText": " Snake in the grass"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80381,
    "questionText": " Safe and sound",
    "answerText": " Safely"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80382,
    "questionText": " Slip of the tongue",
    "answerText": " A mistake of speech"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80383,
    "questionText": " 12. Slip of the pen",
    "answerText": " A small unintentional mistake in writing"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80384,
    "questionText": " U. So long as",
    "answerText": " Until"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80385,
    "questionText": " 1-1. Shortcut"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80386,
    "questionText": " 15. See eye to eye"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80387,
    "questionText": " 16. Send word",
    "answerText": " To send the message"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80388,
    "questionText": " 17. Show of hand",
    "answerText": " Lifting the hand"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80389,
    "questionText": " Scot free",
    "answerText": " To go without punishment"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80390,
    "questionText": " Seasoned food",
    "answerText": " Spicy food"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80391,
    "questionText": " See the light",
    "answerText": " To be born"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80392,
    "questionText": " Set one's scheme on foot",
    "answerText": " To start a plan"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80393,
    "questionText": " Set at liberty",
    "answerText": " To release"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80394,
    "questionText": " Set one's face against",
    "answerText": " To Oppose sternly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80395,
    "questionText": " Set one's heart on",
    "answerText": " To like more and more"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80396,
    "questionText": " Set one's teeth on edge",
    "answerText": " To bear contemptation or hatred"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80397,
    "questionText": " Shut one's mouth",
    "answerText": " To keep silent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80398,
    "questionText": " Slip through one's fingers",
    "answerText": " To come out of the hand"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80399,
    "questionText": " Spare time"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80400,
    "questionText": " To stand on one's own ground",
    "answerText": " To maintain one's own position"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80401,
    "questionText": " A stone's throw",
    "answerText": " Very-near"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80402,
    "questionText": " Strike a bargain",
    "answerText": " To deal in business"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80403,
    "questionText": " Sworn enemies",
    "answerText": " A staunch enemy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80404,
    "questionText": " Tooth and nail",
    "answerText": " With all one's resources or energy; fiercely; violently"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80405,
    "questionText": " Talk big",
    "answerText": " To admire oneself"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80406,
    "questionText": " Time and again"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80407,
    "questionText": " To and fro",
    "answerText": " backwards and forwards"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80408,
    "questionText": " Take to one's heels",
    "answerText": " Torun away"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80409,
    "questionText": " Tall talk",
    "answerText": " To boast; boastful and exaggerated talk"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80410,
    "questionText": " To the letter",
    "answerText": " As same as"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80411,
    "questionText": " Turn over a new leaf",
    "answerText": " To start a new life"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80412,
    "questionText": " Through thick and thin",
    "answerText": " In all circumstances"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80413,
    "questionText": " Throw cold water",
    "answerText": " To discourage"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80414,
    "questionText": " Through and through",
    "answerText": " Completely"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80415,
    "questionText": " To the last farthing",
    "answerText": " One by one paisa"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80416,
    "questionText": " To his face"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80417,
    "questionText": " To the utmost"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80418,
    "questionText": " To the point"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80419,
    "questionText": " Take advantage of",
    "answerText": " To get benefit"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80420,
    "questionText": " Take effect",
    "answerText": " To be effected"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80421,
    "questionText": " Take into one's hand",
    "answerText": " To think or to believe"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80422,
    "questionText": " Take something in one's hand",
    "answerText": " To take responsibility in one's hand"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80423,
    "questionText": " Take heart",
    "answerText": " To have courage"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80424,
    "questionText": " 21. Testing time",
    "answerText": " A period of examination"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80425,
    "questionText": " 22. This and that",
    "answerText": " To and fro"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80426,
    "questionText": " 23. Think twice",
    "answerText": " To decide carefully"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80427,
    "questionText": " 24. Take stock of",
    "answerText": " To survey"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80428,
    "questionText": " The Three R's"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80429,
    "questionText": " Take notice"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80430,
    "questionText": " Take the chair",
    "answerText": " To be a chairman"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80431,
    "questionText": " Take care of",
    "answerText": " To look after-to be alert"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80432,
    "questionText": " Take hold of",
    "answerText": " To catch"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80433,
    "questionText": " Take someone in to confidence"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80434,
    "questionText": " Take place"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80435,
    "questionText": " 32. Take part in",
    "answerText": " To participate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80436,
    "questionText": " Throw dust in one's eyes"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80437,
    "questionText": " Take a fancy",
    "answerText": " To like very much"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80438,
    "questionText": " Take a leap in the dark",
    "answerText": " An action or a risk that you take without knowing anything about the activity or what the result will be"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80439,
    "questionText": " 36. Take by storm",
    "answerText": " To conquer rapidly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80440,
    "questionText": " 37. Take into account",
    "answerText": " To take into consideration"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80441,
    "questionText": " Take one at his word",
    "answerText": " To believe on saying anyone"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80442,
    "questionText": " Take one's time"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80443,
    "questionText": " Take oneself off",
    "answerText": " To walk away"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80444,
    "questionText": " Take sides",
    "answerText": " To support one in quarrelling of the two"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80445,
    "questionText": " Take the air",
    "answerText": " To walk in the open air"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80446,
    "questionText": " Take the bull by the horns",
    "answerText": " To face a difficulty boldly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80447,
    "questionText": " Take the law into one's hands",
    "answerText": " To punish somebody with his hands"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80448,
    "questionText": " Take time off",
    "answerText": " To take leave"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80449,
    "questionText": " 46. Take to heart",
    "answerText": " To feel with heart"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80450,
    "questionText": " 47. Take to task"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80451,
    "questionText": " 48. Throwaway money",
    "answerText": " To spend carelessly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80452,
    "questionText": " 49. Time after time",
    "answerText": " Frequently-repeatedly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80453,
    "questionText": " 50. Turn up one's nose at",
    "answerText": " To regard with contempt"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80454,
    "questionText": " Up to the mark",
    "answerText": " Up to a certain standard"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80455,
    "questionText": " Ups and downs",
    "answerText": " Good and bad times"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80456,
    "questionText": " An uphill task",
    "answerText": " A difficult work"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80457,
    "questionText": " Up and doing",
    "answerText": " Active in work"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80458,
    "questionText": " Under consideration",
    "answerText": " Being discussed"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80459,
    "questionText": " Under lock and key"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80460,
    "questionText": " Under the nose",
    "answerText": " Inclose vicinity"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80461,
    "questionText": " Under the nose of",
    "answerText": " Almost in the presence of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80462,
    "questionText": " Up-to-date"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80463,
    "questionText": " Up in arms",
    "answerText": " to be ready to fight with"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80464,
    "questionText": " Under a cloud",
    "answerText": " In suspicion. in disfavour ordisgrace"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80465,
    "questionText": " Upon one's sweet will",
    "answerText": " On one's desire or wish"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80466,
    "questionText": " 13. Under the rose",
    "answerText": " Secretly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80467,
    "questionText": " 14. Upper hand"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80468,
    "questionText": " 15. Up to time"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80469,
    "questionText": " 16. Under the sun",
    "answerText": " Anywhere"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80470,
    "questionText": " Under the embargo",
    "answerText": " Under impediment"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80471,
    "questionText": " Under the wing",
    "answerText": " Under the protection"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80472,
    "questionText": " Uneasy about for",
    "answerText": " To be anxious about"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80473,
    "questionText": " Utter failure",
    "answerText": " Extreme failure"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80474,
    "questionText": " Vice versa",
    "answerText": " The other way round"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80475,
    "questionText": " Vis-a-vis",
    "answerText": " In relation to"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80476,
    "questionText": " View with",
    "answerText": " To complete"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80477,
    "questionText": " A vexed question",
    "answerText": " A complicated problem"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80478,
    "questionText": " Vet for",
    "answerText": " To examine someone's record"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80479,
    "questionText": " Via tria, via tuta"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80480,
    "questionText": " With a view to",
    "answerText": " For the purpose of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80481,
    "questionText": " Without fail",
    "answerText": " Undoubtly; definitely"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80482,
    "questionText": " In/with reference to",
    "answerText": " Used to say what you are talking or writing about"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80483,
    "questionText": " With respect to something",
    "answerText": " Concerning"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80484,
    "questionText": " Ways and means"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80485,
    "questionText": " Why and wherefore"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80486,
    "questionText": " Worship the rising sun",
    "answerText": " To honour anew impressive or successful person; to respect the man who is rising in power"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80487,
    "questionText": " With might and main"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80488,
    "questionText": " With a vengeance",
    "answerText": " Excessively"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80489,
    "questionText": " Wide of the mark",
    "answerText": " Besides the purpose"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80490,
    "questionText": " A white elephant",
    "answerText": " An expensive burdensome but useless thing; A very expensive thing"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80491,
    "questionText": " All well and good",
    "answerText": " Quite good but not exactly what is wanted"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80492,
    "questionText": " 15. What's what",
    "answerText": " The true position of affairs"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80493,
    "questionText": " Wheels within wheels",
    "answerText": " Complication"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80494,
    "questionText": " 17. Within an ace of",
    "answerText": " Almost to be nearly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80495,
    "questionText": " 18. A wolf in sheep's clothing"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80496,
    "questionText": " 19. Worn out",
    "answerText": " To discover by persistent questioning"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80497,
    "questionText": " Will and pleasure",
    "answerText": " Desire or wish"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80498,
    "questionText": " 21. With one voice",
    "answerText": " As a group; with everyone agreeing; unanimously"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80499,
    "questionText": " 22. A warm reception",
    "answerText": " To receive cordially"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80500,
    "questionText": " 23. Without reserve",
    "answerText": " Without hiding a matter"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80501,
    "questionText": " Well to do",
    "answerText": " Rich"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80502,
    "questionText": " Well-off",
    "answerText": " In good circumstances"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80503,
    "questionText": " Walls have ears",
    "answerText": " To listen by someone in disguise"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80504,
    "questionText": " Walk the streets"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80505,
    "questionText": " 28. While away",
    "answerText": " To waste time; to pass time in amusement"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80506,
    "questionText": " White lie",
    "answerText": " A blunt lie"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80507,
    "questionText": " 30. Win laurels",
    "answerText": " To distinguish oneself"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80508,
    "questionText": " 31. Wipe off",
    "answerText": " To clean by rubbing with cloth"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80509,
    "questionText": " 32. With good grace",
    "answerText": " Willingly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80510,
    "questionText": " 33. With one accord",
    "answerText": " Agreeing together"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80511,
    "questionText": " 34. Without an exception",
    "answerText": " for every one"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80512,
    "questionText": " 35. A word in one's ears",
    "answerText": " To say in private"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80513,
    "questionText": " 36. Weal and woe",
    "answerText": " In prosperity and adversity"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80514,
    "questionText": " 37. Wear and tear",
    "answerText": " Decrease in value due to constant use"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80515,
    "questionText": " Worth while",
    "answerText": " Proper"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80516,
    "questionText": " A wind goose chase",
    "answerText": " A foolish and useless search"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80517,
    "questionText": " 40. Towin the pal:m",
    "answerText": " To win a prize"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80518,
    "questionText": " Year by year",
    "answerText": " Yearly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80519,
    "questionText": " 2. Yeoman service",
    "answerText": " An excellent work"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80520,
    "questionText": " 3. Yet again",
    "answerText": " Once more"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80521,
    "questionText": " 4. Yoke of opinion",
    "answerText": " Force of public opinion"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80522,
    "questionText": " 5. Yellow boy",
    "answerText": " A gold coin"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80523,
    "questionText": " 6. Yellow brick road"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80524,
    "questionText": " Zig-zag",
    "answerText": " Not straight"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80525,
    "questionText": " At random",
    "answerText": " Aimlessly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80526,
    "questionText": " At first sight",
    "answerText": " At the first meeting"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80527,
    "questionText": " Above all",
    "answerText": " More than anything else"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80528,
    "questionText": " At a discount",
    "answerText": " Declining"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80529,
    "questionText": " Above board",
    "answerText": " Openly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80530,
    "questionText": " Apple of one's eye",
    "answerText": " An object of love"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80531,
    "questionText": " Apple of discord",
    "answerText": " Cause of quarrel"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80532,
    "questionText": " Apple pie order",
    "answerText": " In perfect order"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80533,
    "questionText": " An axe to grind",
    "answerText": " Selfish motive"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80534,
    "questionText": " At one's wit's end",
    "answerText": " To be in a confusion"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80535,
    "questionText": " At an arm's length",
    "answerText": " To keep at a distance"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80536,
    "questionText": " To add fuel to the fire",
    "answerText": " To increase anger"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80537,
    "questionText": " At a stone's throw",
    "answerText": " Ve.zynear"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80538,
    "questionText": " At a loss",
    "answerText": " To be puzzled"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80539,
    "questionText": " As a matter of fact",
    "answerText": " Really"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80540,
    "questionText": " At all hazards",
    "answerText": " In spite of risks"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80541,
    "questionText": " At hand",
    "answerText": " Near"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80542,
    "questionText": " At all events",
    "answerText": " Positively"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80543,
    "questionText": " At sea",
    "answerText": " Weak"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80544,
    "questionText": " Afeather in the cup",
    "answerText": " A very good achievement"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80545,
    "questionText": " As a rule",
    "answerText": " Usually"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80546,
    "questionText": " All in all",
    "answerText": " The most important and powerful person"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80547,
    "questionText": " At sixes and sevens",
    "answerText": " In disorder"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80548,
    "questionText": " Man of Iron",
    "answerText": " A man of strong will power"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80549,
    "questionText": " To show white feather",
    "answerText": " To show fear"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80550,
    "questionText": " At the eleventh hour",
    "answerText": " At the last moment"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80551,
    "questionText": " To rise like a phoenix",
    "answerText": " To start a fresh from as low position"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80552,
    "questionText": " To meet one's waterloo",
    "answerText": " To meet one's defeat"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80553,
    "questionText": " High and dry",
    "answerText": " Isolated"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80554,
    "questionText": " To bury the hatchet",
    "answerText": " To make peace"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80555,
    "questionText": " To set the Thames on fire",
    "answerText": " Surprising things"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80556,
    "questionText": " To put the cat among pigeons",
    "answerText": " To be placed in a wrong situation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80557,
    "questionText": " To sound a red alert",
    "answerText": " To make alert"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80558,
    "questionText": " To beat about the bush",
    "answerText": " To talk about unimportant things"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80559,
    "questionText": " A boon in disguise",
    "answerText": " A benefit in loss"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80560,
    "questionText": " A big shot",
    "answerText": " Important person"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80561,
    "questionText": " To play ducks and drake",
    "answerText": " To squander money"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80562,
    "questionText": " To break the duck",
    "answerText": " To begin"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80563,
    "questionText": " To die a dog's death",
    "answerText": " Unheroic death"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80564,
    "questionText": " Rise from ashes",
    "answerText": " To rise from low"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80565,
    "questionText": " My hands are full",
    "answerText": " I am busy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80566,
    "questionText": " To give someone a piece of mind",
    "answerText": " To scold"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80567,
    "questionText": " A bull in the china shop",
    "answerText": " An awkward person"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80568,
    "questionText": " To get away with",
    "answerText": " To escape"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80569,
    "questionText": " To kick one's heels",
    "answerText": " To waste time"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80570,
    "questionText": " Make hay while the sun shines",
    "answerText": " To make best use of favourable opportunities"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80571,
    "questionText": " To put a spoke in one's wheel",
    "answerText": " To disturb"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80572,
    "questionText": " Fancy price",
    "answerText": " High price"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80573,
    "questionText": " Fair-weather friends",
    "answerText": " Friends only in good days"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80574,
    "questionText": " Far and wide",
    "answerText": " All around"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80575,
    "questionText": " Hole and comer policy",
    "answerText": " Improper policy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80576,
    "questionText": " Cut no ice",
    "answerText": " To make no effect"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80577,
    "questionText": " Hand in glove",
    "answerText": " Close friendship"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80578,
    "questionText": " To work like a dog",
    "answerText": " To work very hard"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80579,
    "questionText": " To keep one's fingers crossed",
    "answerText": " Wishing good for somebody"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80580,
    "questionText": " To keep the wolf away from the door",
    "answerText": " To keep off poverty from oneself"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80581,
    "questionText": " A red letter day.",
    "answerText": " An important day"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80582,
    "questionText": " To have several irons in the fire",
    "answerText": " To have many pieces of work"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80583,
    "questionText": " Pull the wool over somebody's eyes",
    "answerText": " To deceive"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80584,
    "questionText": " A blue book",
    "answerText": " A government report"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80585,
    "questionText": " To feather's one's nest",
    "answerText": " To provide money even dishonestly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80586,
    "questionText": " Odds and ends",
    "answerText": " Various articles"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80587,
    "questionText": " A hot line",
    "answerText": " Direct telephone line between Heads of states"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80588,
    "questionText": " To read between the lines",
    "answerText": " To understand more than the actual"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80589,
    "questionText": " Feet of clay",
    "answerText": " To be weak"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80590,
    "questionText": " A mare's nest",
    "answerText": " A discovery which looks valuable"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80591,
    "questionText": " To stand one's guns",
    "answerText": " To preserve when hardships press"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80592,
    "questionText": " To throw up one's nose at a thing",
    "answerText": " Disgust"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80593,
    "questionText": " A lady's man",
    "answerText": " A lover of woman's company"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80594,
    "questionText": " A baker's dozen",
    "answerText": " Thirteen"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80595,
    "questionText": " To clinch the issue",
    "answerText": " Decide"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80596,
    "questionText": " To turn the corner",
    "answerText": " Pass the crisis"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80597,
    "questionText": " To rock the boat",
    "answerText": " Upset the balance"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80598,
    "questionText": " To chew the cuds",
    "answerText": " To muse on"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80599,
    "questionText": " A duck in a thunderstorm",
    "answerText": " Distressed"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80600,
    "questionText": " A man of the world"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80601,
    "questionText": " Midas touch",
    "answerText": " Ability to succeed in all projects"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80602,
    "questionText": " To come down in the world",
    "answerText": " To lose one's social and financial position"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80603,
    "questionText": " To cut both ends",
    "answerText": " To argue in support of both sides of the issue"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80604,
    "questionText": " A sleeping partner",
    "answerText": " An inactive business partner"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80605,
    "questionText": " French leave",
    "answerText": " Absence without permission"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80606,
    "questionText": " An arm chair job",
    "answerText": " An easy and well paid regular job"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80607,
    "questionText": " Run of the mill",
    "answerText": " Ordinary"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80608,
    "questionText": " Hole and corner",
    "answerText": " Secret"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80609,
    "questionText": " Hammer and sickle",
    "answerText": " Emblem of socialism"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80610,
    "questionText": " Meek and mild",
    "answerText": " Gentle and mind"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80611,
    "questionText": " Back stairs gossip",
    "answerText": " Gossip among servants"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80612,
    "questionText": " To bell the cat",
    "answerText": " To take great personal risk"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80613,
    "questionText": " To bite the dust",
    "answerText": " Tosuffer defeat"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80614,
    "questionText": " To be in the driving seat",
    "answerText": " In control"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80615,
    "questionText": " To cross swords",
    "answerText": " To enter into a dispute"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80616,
    "questionText": " To cut a sorry figure",
    "answerText": " To create poor impression"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80617,
    "questionText": " To die in harness",
    "answerText": " To die while actively engaged in one's regular work"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80618,
    "questionText": " To get into hot water",
    "answerText": " To get into difficulties"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80619,
    "questionText": " To egg on",
    "answerText": " To urge on"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80620,
    "questionText": " To drive at",
    "answerText": " To employ"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80621,
    "questionText": " To go through fire and water",
    "answerText": " To pass through difficulties"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80622,
    "questionText": " To go to dogs",
    "answerText": " To be ruined"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80623,
    "questionText": " To hang fire",
    "answerText": " To hesitate"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80624,
    "questionText": " To keep one's card close to one's chest",
    "answerText": " Be secretive"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80625,
    "questionText": " To hit below the belt",
    "answerText": " Give an unfair blow"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80626,
    "questionText": " To hit the jackpot",
    "answerText": " To have a big success"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80627,
    "questionText": " To jump to a conclusion",
    "answerText": " To arrive on a conclusion without justification"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80628,
    "questionText": " To keep the ball rolling",
    "answerText": " To maintain progress"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80629,
    "questionText": " To let oneself go",
    "answerText": " To allow emotionally"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80630,
    "questionText": " To lead a cat and dog's life",
    "answerText": " To quarrel constantly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80631,
    "questionText": " To knock the bottom out of",
    "answerText": " To make a scheme"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80632,
    "questionText": " To make good",
    "answerText": " To repair"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80633,
    "questionText": " To miss the bus/boat",
    "answerText": " To lose an opportunity"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80634,
    "questionText": " To make one's blood cold",
    "answerText": " To frighten"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80635,
    "questionText": " To make both ends meet",
    "answerText": " To live within one's income"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80636,
    "questionText": " To make a mountain out of a mole hill",
    "answerText": " To exaggerate a small matter"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80637,
    "questionText": " To look through coloured glasses",
    "answerText": " To see things not as they are"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80638,
    "questionText": " To look off colours",
    "answerText": " Seem unwell"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80639,
    "questionText": " To look black at somebody",
    "answerText": " Look at him angrily"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80640,
    "questionText": " To kick up a row",
    "answerText": " To create a disturbance"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80641,
    "questionText": " By far",
    "answerText": " Beyond all comparison"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80642,
    "questionText": " To bear a grudge",
    "answerText": " To have better feeling"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80643,
    "questionText": " By dint of",
    "answerText": " By means of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80644,
    "questionText": " By no means",
    "answerText": " In no way"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80645,
    "questionText": " By virtue of",
    "answerText": " On account of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80646,
    "questionText": " By all means",
    "answerText": " Certainly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80647,
    "questionText": " Bag and baggage",
    "answerText": " Completely"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80648,
    "questionText": " To blow one's own trumpet",
    "answerText": " To speak proudly of oneself"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80649,
    "questionText": " Back out",
    "answerText": " To break a promise"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80650,
    "questionText": " Bad blood",
    "answerText": " Enmity"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80651,
    "questionText": " Blue blood",
    "answerText": " Noble blood"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80652,
    "questionText": " To break the ice",
    "answerText": " To break the silence"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80653,
    "questionText": " By leaps and bounds",
    "answerText": " Rapidly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80654,
    "questionText": " To bum the candle at both ends"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80655,
    "questionText": " By hook or by crook",
    "answerText": " By all means"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80656,
    "questionText": " To burn the midnight oil",
    "answerText": " To work very hard till1ateatnight"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80657,
    "questionText": " Below one's dignity",
    "answerText": " Below one's position"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80658,
    "questionText": " Beside the mark",
    "answerText": " Not to the point"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80659,
    "questionText": " A brown study",
    "answerText": " Dreaming"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80660,
    "questionText": " A burning question",
    "answerText": " An important question"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80661,
    "questionText": " A black sheep",
    "answerText": " A disgraceful person"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80662,
    "questionText": " A broken reed",
    "answerText": " An independent person/thing"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80663,
    "questionText": " A bird's eye view",
    "answerText": " A general study/view"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80664,
    "questionText": " 153. To carry the day",
    "answerText": " To succeed"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80665,
    "questionText": " 154. To beggar description",
    "answerText": " Beyond description"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80666,
    "questionText": " 155. Birds of a feather",
    "answerText": " Persons having the same professions"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80667,
    "questionText": " 156. To beat hollow",
    "answerText": " To defeat completely"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80668,
    "questionText": " 157. To bear the brunt of",
    "answerText": " To bear the consequences"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80669,
    "questionText": " 150. A bed of thorns",
    "answerText": " Full of sufferings and sorrows"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80670,
    "questionText": " 159. A bed of roses",
    "answerText": " Full of joy and pleasures"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80671,
    "questionText": " Between the devil and the deep sea",
    "answerText": " Between two great difficulties"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80672,
    "questionText": " To the backbone",
    "answerText": " Thoroughly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80673,
    "questionText": " 162. A bird of passage",
    "answerText": " A migratory person"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80674,
    "questionText": " 163. To build castles in the air",
    "answerText": " To form imaginary schemes"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80675,
    "questionText": " 164. Bread and butter",
    "answerText": " Livelihood"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80676,
    "questionText": " 165. To come to hand",
    "answerText": " Receive"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80677,
    "questionText": " 166. A eat's paw",
    "answerText": " To make somebody a fool"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80678,
    "questionText": " 167. A cock and bull story",
    "answerText": " An imaginary story"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80679,
    "questionText": " 16R. To burn one's fingers",
    "answerText": " To get into trouble"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80680,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80681,
    "questionText": "          ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80682,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": " , ,   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80683,
    "questionText": " 169. To burn one's boats",
    "answerText": " To decide"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80684,
    "questionText": " 170. A cool head",
    "answerText": " A calm judgement"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80685,
    "questionText": " 171. To cry for the moon",
    "answerText": " To wish for something impossible"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80686,
    "questionText": "  ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80687,
    "questionText": " 172. To catch red-handed",
    "answerText": " To catch in the act of doing"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80688,
    "questionText": " 173. To come to grief",
    "answerText": " To be ruined/to fail"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80689,
    "questionText": "  ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80690,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80691,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80692,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": " 50 cm"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80693,
    "questionText": "  ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80694,
    "questionText": "  ? ",
    "answerText": " ,  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80695,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": 22
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80696,
    "questionText": " 174. To cut a sorry figure",
    "answerText": " To produce a poor result"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80697,
    "questionText": " 17;. Crocodile tears",
    "answerText": " False tears"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80698,
    "questionText": " 176. A child's play",
    "answerText": " Something very easy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80699,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": " ,  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80700,
    "questionText": " 177. To come of age",
    "answerText": " To be major"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80701,
    "questionText": " 178. To carry fire and sword",
    "answerText": " To cause destruction"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80702,
    "questionText": " 179. To cry over spilt milk",
    "answerText": " To reach a crisis"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80703,
    "questionText": " 180. To change hands",
    "answerText": " To pass from one person to another"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80704,
    "questionText": " I8I. To come to a head",
    "answerText": " To reach a crisis"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80705,
    "questionText": " 182. To cross swords",
    "answerText": " To fight"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80706,
    "questionText": " I83. To clinch the issue",
    "answerText": " To decide the matter"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80707,
    "questionText": " 184. To chew the cud",
    "answerText": " To think deeply"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80708,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80709,
    "questionText": " A cry in the wilderness",
    "answerText": " A useless cry"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80710,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80711,
    "questionText": " Cast down",
    "answerText": " Depressed"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80712,
    "questionText": " To feather one's nest",
    "answerText": " To care for one's selfish interest"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80713,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80714,
    "questionText": " By fits and starts",
    "answerText": " Irregularly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80715,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80716,
    "questionText": " , ,     ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80717,
    "questionText": " A dead letter",
    "answerText": " No longer in use"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80718,
    "questionText": " A dark horse",
    "answerText": " A competition of unknown capabilities"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80719,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80720,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": " ,  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80721,
    "questionText": " To dance to one's tune",
    "answerText": " To carry out orders"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80722,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80723,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80724,
    "questionText": " Sword of Damocles",
    "answerText": " Imminent danger"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80725,
    "questionText": " A drug in the market",
    "answerText": " An unsaleable thing due to lack of demand"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80726,
    "questionText": " Every inch",
    "answerText": " Completely"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80727,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  ,  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80728,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80729,
    "questionText": " A fair weather friend",
    "answerText": " A selfish friend"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80730,
    "questionText": " Eye for eye",
    "answerText": " Tit for tat"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80731,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80732,
    "questionText": " A drawn game",
    "answerText": " In which no team wins"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80733,
    "questionText": " Cat walk disease   ? ",
    "answerText": "    "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80734,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80735,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80736,
    "questionText": "  ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80737,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80738,
    "questionText": "  ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80739,
    "questionText": "       ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80740,
    "questionText": " From hand to mouth",
    "answerText": " A miserable existence"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80741,
    "questionText": " Fed up",
    "answerText": " To be tired of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80742,
    "questionText": " A fish out of water",
    "answerText": " To be in an uncomfortable position"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80743,
    "questionText": " A fool's paradise",
    "answerText": " Joy based on false hopes"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80744,
    "questionText": " To face the music",
    "answerText": " To face trouble"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80745,
    "questionText": " To fish in troubled waters",
    "answerText": " To take advantage of the troubles of others"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80746,
    "questionText": " To give a slip",
    "answerText": " To escape"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80747,
    "questionText": " First and foremost",
    "answerText": " Important"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80748,
    "questionText": " A fly visit",
    "answerText": " Hasty and brief visit"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80749,
    "questionText": " Foul play",
    "answerText": " Bad intention"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80750,
    "questionText": " A fatal disease",
    "answerText": " A disease that causes death"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80751,
    "questionText": " A gala day",
    "answerText": " A day of rejoicings"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80752,
    "questionText": " To get the sack",
    "answerText": " To be dismissed"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80753,
    "questionText": " Togo without saying",
    "answerText": " To be clear"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80754,
    "questionText": " To go a long way",
    "answerText": " A great help"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80755,
    "questionText": " Give and take",
    "answerText": " Mutual co-operation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80756,
    "questionText": " Togo through fire and water",
    "answerText": " To make sacrifice"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80757,
    "questionText": " To grease the palm",
    "answerText": " To bribe"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80758,
    "questionText": " To go hand to hand",
    "answerText": " To go together"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80759,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "     "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80760,
    "questionText": " To gain ground",
    "answerText": " To progress"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80761,
    "questionText": " To be a good hand at",
    "answerText": " To be expert"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80762,
    "questionText": " Hand to hand",
    "answerText": " A close fight"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80763,
    "questionText": " Hide and seek",
    "answerText": " To deceive"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80764,
    "questionText": " Heart to heart",
    "answerText": " Free and frank"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80765,
    "questionText": " High spirits",
    "answerText": " To be very happy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80766,
    "questionText": " Half hearted",
    "answerText": " Lacking enthusiasm"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80767,
    "questionText": "   ..  ? ",
    "answerText": " ... "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80768,
    "questionText": " The high and the low",
    "answerText": " Of all ranks"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80769,
    "questionText": " Hammer and tongs",
    "answerText": " With all one's might"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80770,
    "questionText": " Hale and hearty",
    "answerText": " Very healthy end sound"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80771,
    "questionText": " Hue and cry",
    "answerText": " To raise alarm"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80772,
    "questionText": " A hard nut to crack",
    "answerText": " A problem difficult to solve"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80773,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": " 1962  24 "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80774,
    "questionText": " Heart and soul",
    "answerText": " With full energy"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80775,
    "questionText": " To hammer out",
    "answerText": " To plan"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80776,
    "questionText": " To have a hand in",
    "answerText": " To take part"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80777,
    "questionText": " To have clean hands",
    "answerText": " To be innocent"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80778,
    "questionText": " 236. To hit the nail on the head",
    "answerText": " To do what is proper at a proper time"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80779,
    "questionText": " 237. Hen-pecked",
    "answerText": " A husband under the control of his wife"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80780,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80781,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": " 1542  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80782,
    "questionText": " 238. To have a windfall",
    "answerText": " An unexpected good fortune"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80783,
    "questionText": " 239. Hush money",
    "answerText": " A bribe"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80784,
    "questionText": " 240. Head and shoulders",
    "answerText": " Very superior"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80785,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80786,
    "questionText": " 241. To have finger in the pie",
    "answerText": " To interfere"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80787,
    "questionText": "  ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80788,
    "questionText": " 242. Head and ears",
    "answerText": " Completely"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80789,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "     "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80790,
    "questionText": " 243. Hand and glove with",
    "answerText": " Very friendly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80791,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": " , "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80792,
    "questionText": " 244. Hard and fast",
    "answerText": " Rigid"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80793,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80794,
    "questionText": " 245. To hold one's own",
    "answerText": " To maintain one's position boldly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80795,
    "questionText": " 246. To have one's way",
    "answerText": " To do one's own will"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80796,
    "questionText": " 247. Hobson's choice",
    "answerText": " No choice at all"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80797,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": " ..  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80798,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": " ..  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80799,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80800,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80801,
    "questionText": " 248. To hold one's tongue",
    "answerText": " To keep silence"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80802,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80803,
    "questionText": " 249. In the long run",
    "answerText": " In the end"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80804,
    "questionText": " 250. In a nutshell",
    "answerText": " Briefly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80805,
    "questionText": " 251. An iron hand",
    "answerText": " Severe hand"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80806,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80807,
    "questionText": " 1857    ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80808,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "    "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80809,
    "questionText": "        ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80810,
    "questionText": " 1857     ? ",
    "answerText": "  ,  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80811,
    "questionText": " 252. In the nick of time",
    "answerText": " Justin time"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80812,
    "questionText": " 1954    ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80813,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "    "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80814,
    "questionText": "        ? ",
    "answerText": " , , "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80815,
    "questionText": " 1947  26       ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80816,
    "questionText": " 253. To be in vogue",
    "answerText": " To be in fashion"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80817,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": " . .  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80818,
    "questionText": " 254. In the air",
    "answerText": " Widespread"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80819,
    "questionText": "        ? ",
    "answerText": " . .  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80820,
    "questionText": " ..  ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80821,
    "questionText": " 10 + 2 + 3      ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80822,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80823,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80824,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80825,
    "questionText": " 255. In black and white",
    "answerText": " In writing"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80826,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "     "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80827,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": 1973
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80828,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80829,
    "questionText": "         ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80830,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": 2004
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80831,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": " , , , , , ,  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80832,
    "questionText": " 256. In cold blood",
    "answerText": " Cruelty"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80833,
    "questionText": "      ? ",
    "answerText": " .  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80834,
    "questionText": " 257. Ins and outs",
    "answerText": " Full details"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80835,
    "questionText": " 258. In the course of",
    "answerText": " During"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80836,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": " .. "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80837,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80838,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  ..  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80839,
    "questionText": " 259. In hot water",
    "answerText": " In difficulty"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80840,
    "questionText": "      ? ",
    "answerText": " ....  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80841,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": 1901
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80842,
    "questionText": " 26,1 Jack of all trades",
    "answerText": " A person supposed to know everything but master of none"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80843,
    "questionText": " 261. A jail bird",
    "answerText": " A person who has been to jail many times"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80844,
    "questionText": " 262. Kith and kin",
    "answerText": " Relatives"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80845,
    "questionText": " To keep body and soul together",
    "answerText": " To remain alive"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80846,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80847,
    "questionText": "      ? ",
    "answerText": "  ,   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80848,
    "questionText": "      ? ",
    "answerText": "    "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80849,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80850,
    "questionText": " To keep the wolf from",
    "answerText": " To keep away hunger and the door starvation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80851,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": " 1961  12 "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80852,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80853,
    "questionText": " 265. Knit one's brow",
    "answerText": " To get angry"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80854,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "   11 "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80855,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80856,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80857,
    "questionText": " 266. To keep one's head above water",
    "answerText": " To escape debt"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80858,
    "questionText": " To knock down",
    "answerText": " Bad defeat"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80859,
    "questionText": "          ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80860,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "     "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80861,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": " 1951 "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80862,
    "questionText": "      ? ",
    "answerText": " ..  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80863,
    "questionText": " Lion's share",
    "answerText": " A major share"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80864,
    "questionText": " 269. Letdown",
    "answerText": " To fail to keep promise"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80865,
    "questionText": "  ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80866,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80867,
    "questionText": " 270. To laugh in one's sleeves"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80868,
    "questionText": " 271. Loaves and fishes",
    "answerText": " Material comforts"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80869,
    "questionText": " 272. Let off",
    "answerText": " Released"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80870,
    "questionText": " 273. The long and short",
    "answerText": " In brief"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80871,
    "questionText": " 274. To have no stone unturned",
    "answerText": " To make all possible efforts"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80872,
    "questionText": " 275. To look blue",
    "answerText": " Depressed"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80873,
    "questionText": " 276. To lead astray",
    "answerText": " To misguide"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80874,
    "questionText": " 277. To leap in the dark",
    "answerText": " A careless action"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80875,
    "questionText": " A left-handed compliment",
    "answerText": " A false praise"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80876,
    "questionText": " To lend a hand",
    "answerText": " To help"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80877,
    "questionText": " A man in the street",
    "answerText": " An ordinary person"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80878,
    "questionText": " To mind one's own business",
    "answerText": " To leave other people alone"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80879,
    "questionText": " To make neither head nor tail of",
    "answerText": " Not to understand"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80880,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": " 1950  10  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80881,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80882,
    "questionText": " Maiden speech",
    "answerText": " A speech delivered the first time"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80883,
    "questionText": " To make up one's mind",
    "answerText": " To resolve"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80884,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80885,
    "questionText": " A man of means",
    "answerText": " A rich man"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80886,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "     "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80887,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": 1937
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80888,
    "questionText": " To mince matters",
    "answerText": " Not to talk plainly"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80889,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80890,
    "questionText": "        ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80891,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80892,
    "questionText": " To make a clean sweep of",
    "answerText": " To remove"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80893,
    "questionText": "       ? ",
    "answerText": " ..  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80894,
    "questionText": " A man of moment",
    "answerText": " An important person"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80895,
    "questionText": " A man of word",
    "answerText": " A reliable person"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80896,
    "questionText": " To make headway",
    "answerText": " To progress slowly and steadily"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80897,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80898,
    "questionText": " A nine day's wonder",
    "answerText": " Pleasure for a short period"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80899,
    "questionText": " 293. A necessary evil",
    "answerText": " An unavoidable evil"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80900,
    "questionText": " Out of gear",
    "answerText": " Out of order"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80901,
    "questionText": " 298. Or no avail",
    "answerText": " Of no use"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80902,
    "questionText": " Out of place",
    "answerText": " Not proper to the occasion"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80903,
    "questionText": " Out of date",
    "answerText": " Out of fashion"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80904,
    "questionText": "       ? ",
    "answerText": 1977
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80905,
    "questionText": " 304. On the eve of",
    "answerText": " Just before"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80906,
    "questionText": " Offhand",
    "answerText": " Without previous preparation"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80907,
    "questionText": " Nook and comer",
    "answerText": " Everywhere"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80908,
    "questionText": " To nurse a grudge",
    "answerText": " To revenge"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80909,
    "questionText": " 1948  10 ..    ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80910,
    "questionText": " Neck to neck",
    "answerText": " Side by side"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80911,
    "questionText": "  ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80912,
    "questionText": " .. ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80913,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80914,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80915,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80916,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80917,
    "questionText": "      ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80918,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80919,
    "questionText": " Neck or Nothing",
    "answerText": " With the use of everything"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80920,
    "questionText": " The printer's devils",
    "answerText": " Misprints"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80921,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80922,
    "questionText": " To play the games",
    "answerText": " To observe the rules"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80923,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80924,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80925,
    "questionText": "  ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80926,
    "questionText": " W    ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80927,
    "questionText": " To pick a quarrel",
    "answerText": " Intentionally begin a quarrel"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80928,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "    "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80929,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80930,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80931,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": " 24  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80932,
    "questionText": " Palmy days",
    "answerText": " Prosperous and peaceful days"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80933,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": " 2.37 . /  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80934,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80935,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80936,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80937,
    "questionText": " To put one's shoulders to the wheel",
    "answerText": " To help oneself"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80938,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80939,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80940,
    "questionText": " To put the cart before the horse",
    "answerText": " Reverse order"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80941,
    "questionText": " To pull one's legs",
    "answerText": " To make a fool of"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80942,
    "questionText": " A past master",
    "answerText": " Thorough master"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80943,
    "questionText": " To poke one's nose",
    "answerText": " To interfere with"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80944,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": " ..  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80945,
    "questionText": " To play with fire",
    "answerText": " To do something dangerous"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80946,
    "questionText": " Pass through",
    "answerText": " Undergo"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80947,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80948,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80949,
    "questionText": "      ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80950,
    "questionText": "       ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80951,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": " . - 7 "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80952,
    "questionText": "  ? ",
    "answerText": "  11 "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80953,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "  40 "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80954,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": 12
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80955,
    "questionText": " To pay the piper",
    "answerText": " To bear the cost"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80956,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "  1 "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80957,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80958,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80959,
    "questionText": " ' '    ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80960,
    "questionText": "      ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80961,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80962,
    "questionText": " 325. To put in cold storage",
    "answerText": " To neglect"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80963,
    "questionText": " 126. A queer fish",
    "answerText": " A strange person"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80964,
    "questionText": " 327. To pour oil on troubled waters",
    "answerText": " To pacify matters"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80965,
    "questionText": " 328. A rainy day",
    "answerText": " A time of difficulty"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80966,
    "questionText": " 329. A red letter day",
    "answerText": " Lucky and important day"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80967,
    "questionText": " 330. Root and branch",
    "answerText": " Entirely"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80968,
    "questionText": "  ? ",
    "answerText": "  15 "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80969,
    "questionText": "  ? ",
    "answerText": "  25 "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80970,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": " .. "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80971,
    "questionText": " .. ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80972,
    "questionText": "  ? ",
    "answerText": "   , ,  ,   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80973,
    "questionText": " 331. Torun down",
    "answerText": " Weak in health"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80974,
    "questionText": " ..  ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80975,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": " ..   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80976,
    "questionText": " 332. A red rag to a bull",
    "answerText": " A cause for anger"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80977,
    "questionText": " ..  ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80978,
    "questionText": " 333. Rough and ready",
    "answerText": " Unpolished manners"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80979,
    "questionText": " 334. Red tapism",
    "answerText": " Official formality"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80980,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80981,
    "questionText": "  ? ",
    "answerText": " ,  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80982,
    "questionText": " 335. Round the comer",
    "answerText": " Near"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80983,
    "questionText": " 336. Run through",
    "answerText": " Waste"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80984,
    "questionText": "     ? ",
    "answerText": "  -1 "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80985,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "    "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80986,
    "questionText": "   ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80987,
    "questionText": "  ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80988,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80989,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": "  ..  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80990,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": " ..  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80991,
    "questionText": "      ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80992,
    "questionText": "      ? ",
    "answerText": "  .  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80993,
    "questionText": "       ? ",
    "answerText": " ..  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80994,
    "questionText": "      ? ",
    "answerText": "  .  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80995,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": " 1900   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80996,
    "questionText": "             ? ",
    "answerText": "  "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80997,
    "questionText": " 337. A rolling stone",
    "answerText": " One who is never constant to one's work"
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80998,
    "questionText": "      ? ",
    "answerText": "   "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 80999,
    "questionText": "    ? ",
    "answerText": " 2013  27 "
  },
  {
    "questionNum": 81000,
    "questionText": " 338. A royal road",
    "answerText": " An easy way to achieve an end"
  }
]